A Finding Aid to the Erwin Panofsky Papers, 1904-1990 (bulk dates 1920-1968), in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
- Correspondence, 1921-1978, undated; Series 1; Archival Resource Key; (Boxes 1-16; 16 linear ft. Reels 2108-2128)
  - Colleagues, Scholars, Students and Other Individuals, 1921-1978, undated; 1.1; Archival Resource Key
    - Coolidge, John, 1948-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Constable - Corbett, 1954-1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 9)
      Constable, Giles
      Coor, Gertrude
      Corbett, James
    - Coremans, Paul, 1948-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Reel 10-13)
    - Costello, Jane, 1946-1953; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Covi, Dario Alessandro, 1953-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Craven - Creese, 1952-1962; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 16)
      Craven, Wayne
      Creese, Walter L.
    - Crosby, Sumner, McK., 1941-1956; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Curtis, 1959-1967, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 18)
      Curtis, Ernest Robert
      Curtis, Klaus
    - Cuttler, Charles D., 1948-1957; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - D, General (single letters, Dacos - Dyson), 1937-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 20)
      Dacos, Nichole
      Dallam, John M.
      Daly, L. J.
      David, Alfred
      Davis, Catherine
      Davis, Mrs. H. Chandler
      Davis, Howard
      Davis, Saville R.
      Dazzi, Manlio
      Dean, G. K.
      Dean, R. J.
      De Blanc, George
      De Boer, P.
      De Christoforo
      Dehn, Georg
      Delatour, G. S.
      De Laurier, Nancy Gibbon
      Delius, F.
      Della Vida, G. Levi
      Delman, Emil
      Dencher, Eva
      De Roover, Florence E.
      Dettweiler, Frieda
      Deuchlerl, Florens
      Devisse, J.
      Dickson, T. Elder
      Dieckmann, Liselotte
      Diehl, George K.
      Dihle, A.
      Diller, Hans
      Diez, Ernst
      Dingelstedt, Kurt
      Dochy, J.
      Dodwell, Reginald
      Doeblin, Alfred
      Dolan, James L.
      Donaldson, Katherine
      Donovan, James A., Jr.
      Dorner, Alexander
      Dorner, Lydia A.
      Dorsky, Morris
      Dow, Helen J.
      Downey, Glanville
      Dressler, Fridollin
      Drucker, Peter F.
      Drury, Betty
      Dubiner, Susan
      Duclos, R.
      Dufour, Alain
      Dundas, Judith
      Dyson, Freeman
    - Dahl - Dahlbäck, 1957-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 21)
      Dahl, Brother Thomas More
      Dahlbäck, Bengt
    - D'Ancona, Mirella Levi, 1947-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 22-24)
    - Davies, Martin, 1948-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Dean - Delanoy, 1945-1966, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 26)
      Dean, Ruth J.
      Degenhart, Bernhard
      Deinzer, Willi
      Deknatel, Frederick B.
      Delanoy, Eleanor
    - Delaisé, Léon M. J., 1950-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Dempsey - Dewald, 1954-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 28)
      Dempsey, Charles
      Demus, Otto
      Desneux, Jules
      Dewald, Ernest T.
    - Dhanes - Dieckmann, 1952-1958; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 29)
      Dhanes, Elisabeth
      Dibner, Bern
      Dieckmann, Herbert
    - Dienstfrey - Dobrzeniecki, 1938-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 30)
      Dienstfrey, Debra
      Dinsmoor, William B.
      Dobrzeniecki, Tadeusz
    - Dodd - Downey, 1931-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 31)
      Dodd, Lamar
      Dodgson, Campbell
      Dodwell, Charles Reginald
      Dohmann, Albrecht
      Donati, Lamberto
    - Drake, Stillman, 1955-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Dupont, Jacques, 1952-1963, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Dussler, Luitpold, 1964-1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - E, General (single letters, Eakins - Escala), 1937-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 1)
      Eakins, J. M.
      Earle, Edward Mead
      Edgar, Esabella M.
      Edgar, Sister Mary
      Edgerton
      Edwards, Audrey L.
      Egri
      Ehrman, A.
      Eichenberg, Fritz
      Einstein, Alfred
      Einstein, Norbert
      Eismann, Heinrich
      Eisenberg, Marvin
      Eliasberg, Wladimir G.
      Ellis, Albert
      Emboden, William Al
      Emerson, William
      Emmens, J. A.
      Engelbregt, Father J.H.A.
      Engleson, H.
      Epstein, Marion K.
      Erdberg, Joan Prentice von
      Er-Shih, Chiang
      Erlebacher, Walter
      Erler, Adalbert
      Erskine, Peggy A.
      Escala, Donna N.
    - Ebbingewubben, J. C., 1951-1963; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Edelstein, Ludwig and Renate, 1952-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Eerden - Egan, 1947-1952; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 4)
      Eerden, J. H. van der
      Egan, Patricia
    - Egbert, Donald Drew and Virginia Wylie, 1941-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - de Egrey, Anne, 1956-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Einem, Herbert von, 1953-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Einstein, Albert and Margot, 1938-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Eisenhart, Luther P., 1949-1956; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Eisler, Colin, 1951-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Eissler, K. R., 1957-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Ellenius, Allen, 1957-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Engels - Epstein, 1937-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 13)
      Engels, J.
      Engler, Gustav Andreas
      English, Anne Whitall
      Epstein, Fritz T.
    - Erffa, Hans Martin Feiherr von, 1956-1962; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Erffa, Helmut Freiherr von, 1940-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Esmerian - Ettinghausen, 1942-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 16)
      Esmerian, Ralph O.
      Ettinghausen, Richard
    - Ettlinger, Leopold D., 1953-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Euler, Walter, 1958; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - F, General (single letters, Fagles - Furniss), 1931-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 19-20)
      Fagles, Robert
      Fait, Joachim
      Falkenstein, Henry
      Färber, Helmut
      Fee, James Alger
      Feifel, Herman
      Feltenstein, Rosalie
      Ferguson, Wallace K.
      Fergusson, Francis
      Ferrara, Luisa Balboni-Sindaco di
      Ferrari, Angel
      Ferrari, Guy
      Feron, Madame Raymonde
      Field Enterprises, Inc.
      Filia, Joan
      Filipetto, Gino
      Film, Carin
      Finch, Henry A.
      Fingesten, Peter
      Fink, June-Marie
      Finlayson, Donald L.
      Fischer, L.
      Flagg, Richard B.
      Fleming, John F.
      Fleming, John V.
      Flexner, Abrahae
      Flitner, Wilhelm
      Foelsch
      Folliet, G.
      Foltiny, Stephen
      Forbes, J. D.
      Forbes, Kenneth Ripley
      Foreman, Clark
      Forslund, Erik
      Forth, Robert F.
      Foster, Philip
      Foster, Sharon
      Fowle, J. W.
      Fowler, George
      Fowles, Jean
      Fox, John
      Fox, Milton S.
      Fraenkel, Hans
      Francia, P. L. de
      Francis, William
      Frankena, William
      Frantz, Sally
      Fraser, Russell A.
      Freccero, John
      Freimarck, Vincent
      French and Company, Inc.
      Frenkel, Thomas
      Frey, Dagobert
      Friberg, Axel
      Fried, Alexander
      Friedenwald, Jonas S.
      Fritz, Rolf
      Fröbe-Kapteyn, Olga
      Fulton, John
      Furnies
      Furniss, W. Todd
    - Faglio-dell A'Rco - Federer, 1952-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 21)
      Fagiolo-dell A'Rco, Maurizio and Marcello
      Faison, S. Lane, Jr.
      Federer, Georg
    - Fehl, Philipp, 1955-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Fenyö, Iván, 1960-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Ferguson, Wallace K., 1953-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Fernández, Justino, 1961-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Ferry, W. H., 1962-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Fierz, Marcus, 1955-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Finkelstein - Fisher, 1953-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 28)
      Finkelstein, Louis
      Fiocco, Giuseppe
      Fisher, Martha
    - Fitchen, John F., 1955-1956; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Fogg, John M., Jr., 1951-1952; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Folie, Jacqueline, 1954-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Fong, Wen, 1955-1963; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Fontaine - Forssman, 1954-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 33)
      Fontaine, Mrs. F. D.
      Ford Foundation
      Forssman, Erik
    - Forsyth, George H., Jr., 1946-1965, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Forsyth - Foster, 1951-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 35)
      Forsyth, William H.
      Fosdick, Sina
      Foster, Charles A.
    - Franc, Helen M., 1950-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Francastle - Fränkel, 1946-1959; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 37)
      Francastel, Pierre
      Fränkel, Hermann
    - Frankel - Frankfort, 1951-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 38)
      Frankel, Walter K.
      Frankfort, Henri
    - Frankl, Paul, 1939-1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Frantz - Frenken, 1951-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 40)
      Frantz, Alison
      Freedberg, Sydney
      Frenken, T.W.M.
    - Freudenheim - Friedländer, 1933-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 41)
      Freudenheim, Tom L.
      Freyhan, R.
      Friedländer, Max J.
      Friedländer, Paul
    - Friedländer, Walter, 1932-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 42-43)
    - Friedman, 1936-1955; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 44)
      Friedman, Lionel J.
      Friedman, William F.
    - Friedmann, Herbert, 1945-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - Friend - Fulton, 1952-1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 46)
      Friend, Albert H., Jr.
      Fritz, Kurt von
      Fulton, John F.
    - Gallenkamp - Gutkind (single letters), 1942-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 47)
      Gallenkamp, George V.
      Garbee, Willialm C., Jr.
      Gardie, Krinstina de la
      Garrett, Robert
      Garttmer, Lloyd
      Gellerman, Hersh
      Gellert, Bridget
      Gendler, Rabbi Everett
      Gibson, James J.
      Gilbert, Marianne
      Gilbert, Mary E.
      Gilbert, Philip
      Gilbert, William
      Gillispie, Charles C.
      Gillmer, Vaun
      Gilmore, Gerald F.
      Gilmore, Myron F.
      Ginzburg, Carlo
      Glasser, Hannelore
      Glazier, William S.
      Goldenberg, Anne
      Goldschmidt, Lucien
      Goldstein, C.
      Gonzalez, Joaquin Diaz
      Goris, Jan-Albert
      Gova, Sabine
      Goodall, Donald
      Gottlieb, Carla
      Gottschalk, Louis
      Graubard, Stephen R.
      Graupe, Paul
      Green, P. Charles
      Greenberg, Sidney
      Greenbie, Sydney
      Greene, J. Craig
      Greene, Terrence W.
      Griffin, Gillett
      Griffing, Robert P.
      Griffith, Beatrice Fox
      Grun, Edith
      Guillevic, J.
      Gulamerian, Norman B.
      Gutkind, E. A.
    - Gabriel, Father A. L., 1949-1962; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - Gagnebin-Ganter, 1957-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 49)
      Gagnebin, Bernard
      Galpin, Perrin C.
      Ganter, Joseph
    - Garbáty, 1949-1959; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 50)
      Garbáty, Eugene Leopold
      Garbáty, Maurice
    - Gareis - Garside, 1953-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 51)
      Gareis, Hansgeorg
      Garside, Charles, Jr.
    - Gäumann-Wild - Gauthier, 1956-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 1)
      Gäumann-Wild, Doris
      Gauthier, Marie-Madeline
    - Gelder, Jan G. van, 1951-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 2-3)
    - Gerson, Horst, 1946-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Gessner, Robert, 1948-1961, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Geyl - Giesau, 1924-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 6)
      Geyl, Pieter
      Gibbons, Felton
      Giesau, Hermann
    - Giesey, Ralph E., 1953-1966, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Gilbert, Creighton, 1948-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Gilbert - Godwin, 1942-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 9)
      Gilbert, Felix
      Gnudi, Cesare
      Godwin, Frances Gray
    - Goetz, Oswald, 1950-1953; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Goldberg - Goldman, 1947-1963, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 11)
      Goldberg, Milton
      Goldberg, Norman L.
      Goldman, Hetty
    - Goldschmidt, Adolph, 1924-1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Goldschmidt - Goldwater, 1936-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 13)
      Goldschmidt, Max
      Goldwater, Robert
    - Gombrich, Ernst H., 1946-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Goodchild - Gordon, 1941-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 15)
      Goodchild, Donald
      Goodenough, Erwin R.
      Goodnell, Robert C.
      Gordon, Irene
    - Goris - Gould, 1947-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 16)
      Goris, Jan Albert
      Gosebruch, Martin
      Gottesman, D. S. (D.S. and R.H. Gottesman Foundation)
      Gould, Cecil
    - Graaf - Grange, 1929-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 17)
      Graaf, J. A. van de
      Gradenwitz
      Grange, T. P.
    - Green, Rosalie B., 1954-1967, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Greenbaum - Greene, 1940-1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 19)
      Greenbaum, Edward E.
      Greene, Belle da Costa
    - Greenhaus, Carla, 1962-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Greischel - Griffith, 1956-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 21)
      Greischel, Walther
      Grier, Harry
      Griffith, Charles Francis
      Griffith, Richard
    - Grinten - Grippi, 1951-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 22)
      Grinten, E.F. van der
      Grippi, Rosalind
    - Grodecki, Louis, 1948-1967, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Grosjean - Grote, 1946-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 24)
      Grosjean, Paul
      Grossman, Edwin
      Grote, Ludwig
    - Grenebaum - Guerry, 1948-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 25)
      Grenebaum, L. H.
      de Gruyter, Walter
      Guenther, Peter W.
      Guerlac, Henry
      Guerry, Prosper
    - Gulden - Gwaltney, 1940-1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 26)
      Gulden, Ernst
      Gundersheimer, H.
      Gurewich, Vladimir
      Gutiérrez Mujica, Carlos
      Gutmann, Joseph
      Gwaltney, Corbin
    - H, General (single letters, Hackenbroch - Huth), 1937-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 27-28)
      Hackenbroch, Yvonne
      Hadassah Magazine
      Haering, Irene
      Halberstam, Michael J.
      Halle, Kay
      Hallowell, Robert E.
      Hamberg, Gustav
      Hamburger Frendenblatt
      Hamilton, Thomas H.
      Hanfstaengl, Eberhard
      Harbiso, E. Harris
      Madelean Harmann
      Harrison, Evelyn B.
      Harrison, Frank L.
      Harrsen, Meta
      ???tHart, M. E.
      Hartman, Otto
      Harvey, E. Newton
      Harvey, Marlene
      Harwi, Lawrence
      Häskum, Richard
      Hauben, Janet
      Haufrecht, Betty
      Haugen, Pat
      Haupt, Hans
      Hausmann, U.
      Havenitt, Elaine
      Haverlin, Carl
      Hayek, F. A. von
      Healy, Arthur K. D.
      Hedén, Karl-Gusstaf
      Heemstra, Baron F.S. Sixma van
      Heger, Henrik
      Heidegger
      Heijmans, Eduard
      Heilbrunn, Rudolf M.
      Heinemann, F.
      Heinemann, Rudolf J.
      Heinrich, Ted
      Heisenberg, Werner
      Held, Richard
      Helleiner, Karl T.
      Henderson, George
      Henry, Father Paul
      Herbig, Reinhard
      Herlig,
      Herding, Klaus
      Hernmarck, Carl
      Herring, James V.
      Hersey, Carl K.
      Heyl, Lawrence
      Heymann, Frederick G.
      HiFi/Stereo Review
      Hilweg, Hans
      Hind'Hulsh, R.
      Hinman, Richard L.
      Hirsch, Stefan
      Hoening, Irene
      Hoffeld, Jeffrey M.
      Hoffmann, Konrad
      Hofstede, Justus Müller
      Hohenzollern, Prinz Johann Georg von
      Holborn, Hajo
      Holmqvist, Wilhelm
      Hook, Sidney
      Hootz
      Hopper, Paul
      Horen
      Horizon
      Hoving, Walter
      Howell, Douglass
      Howell, E. B.
      Howell, Warren R.
      Hughes, Serge
      Hugo, Harold
      Humez
      Hupert, Marjorie
      Hürlimann, Caspar G.
      Hürlimann, Hans
      Hurt, Hethro M., III
      Huth, Hans
    - Hahnloser - Hamilton, 1950-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 29)
      Hahnloser, Hans R.
      Haight, Anne
      Haight, Elizabeth Hazelton
      Hamberg, Gustaf
      Hamilton, George Heard
    - Hammer, Victor, 1946-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Hampe - Hanson, 1948-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 31)
      Hampe, Roland
      Hanckel, Hadumoth
      Hanson, Bernard
      Hanson, Norwood R.
    - Harbison, 1944-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 32)
      Harbison, Craig S.
      Harbison, E. Harris
    - Harris - Hartmann, 1951-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 33)
      Harris, Robert M.
      Hartmann, Kurt
    - Hartt, Frederick, 1938-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Hatch - Heath, 1956-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 35)
      Hatch, John Davis
      Hatzfeld, Helmut
      Haussherr, Reiner
      Haycraft, Robert K.
      Heath, William W.
    - Heckscher, William S., 1945-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 36-40)
    - Hermann, Adelheid, 1937-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Heiss - Heitmann, 1931-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 2)
      Heiss, Carl Georg
      Heitmann, Klaus
    - Held, Julius S., 1948-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Helsdingen - Hess, 1938-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 4-5)
      Helsdingen, H. W. van
      Hempel, Eberhard
      Henle, Werner
      Henry, Barklie McKee
      Hentzen, A.
      Hermerén, Göran, undated
      Herrlinger, Robert
      Hertz, Richard
      Hess, Jacob
    - Heydenreich, Ludwig H., 1949-1967, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 6-7)
    - Heyl - Hinks, 1951-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 8)
      Heyl, Bernard C.
      Hibbard, Howard
      Hinks, Roger
    - Hirschfeld, Peter, 1937-1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Hirtum - Hochschild, 1937-1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 10)
      Hirtum, Andrée van
      Hitchcock, Henry-Russell
      Hochschild, Mrs. Harold K.
    - Hofer, Phil, 1946-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Hoff - Hoffmann, 1952-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 12)
      Hoff, Ursula
      Hoffmann, Kathrin
    - Hollander - Holt, 1953-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 13)
      Hollander, John
      Hollister, C. Warren
      Holmback, A.
      Holst, Christian von
      Holt, Mrs. John B.
    - Holzinger - Hope, 1949-1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 14)
      Holzinger, Ernst
      Hoogewerff, G. J.
      Hope, Henry
    - Horb - Horn, 1948-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 15)
      Horb, Felix
      Horn, Walter W.
    - Hornung - Hubala, 1950-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 16)
      Hornung, Hans
      Horváth, Béla
      Houtzager, Maria Elisabeth
      Hubala, Erich
    - d'Hulst, R. A., 1954-1962; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Hungerland - Iklé, 1946-1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 18)
      Hungerland, Helmut
      Hunt, F. L.
      Iklé, Charles F.
    - Ionescu, Theodor, 1958-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Isserstedt - Ivins, 1955-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 20)
      Isserstedt, Dorothea C.
      Ivanoff, Nicolas
      Iversen, Erik
      Ivins, William M., Jr.
    - J, General (single letters, Jacobs - Jung), 1946-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 21)
      Jacobs, Lewis
      Jacobsen, Eric
      Jacquot, Jean
      Jahn, Erich
      Jakobson, Roman
      James, C.L.R.
      Janicik, Edward E. C.
      Janson, Bertil
      Janson, Claire
      Jastrow, Elizabeth
      Jauneau, MaadeleineRocher
      Jauss
      Javet, Pierre
      Jesi, Furio
      Jirat-Wasiutynski, Vojt ch
      John, James J.
      Johnson, Edgar N.
      Johnson, Philip C.
      de Jong, Mrs. H.M.E.
      Jost, Res
      Jung, Eva-Marie
    - James - Jameson, 1954-1956; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 22)
      James, David
      Jaffé, Michael
      James, Mr. and Mrs. William
      Jameson, D.F.B.
    - Janson, H. W., 1936-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 23-25)
    - Jessen - Johnson, 1948-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 26)
      Jessen, H.
      Johnson, James R.
      Johnson, Lee
      Johnson, S. F.
      Johnson, W. McAllister
    - Jones - Jurgen, 1950-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 27)
      Jones, Bob, Jr.
      Jones, Eldred D.
      Josephson, Ragnar
      Jucker, Hans
      Jurgen, Paul
    - K, General (single letters, Kahler - Kuylen), 1948-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 28)
      Kahler, Erich
      Kaizer, Joachim
      Kallen, Horace M. Peter Kamp, van de
      Katona, Paul
      Kaysen, Carl
      Kearns, Helen M.
      Keeper of the King's Pictures
      Keil, Robert A.
      Kellogg, Alfred L.
      Kelly, Leon
      Kennick, William E.
      Kerby-Miller, Charles
      Kern, Paul J.
      Kernodle, George R.
      Kielland, Else Christie
      Kieser, Emil
      Killermann, Sebastian
      Klein, Jerome
      Klimowsky, E. W.
      Knauer, G. Nicholas
      Knipping, J. B.
      Knowlton, Edgar C.
      Knuttel, G.
      Koch, Karl
      Koher, Harris
      Kolb, Albert
      Koslow, Arnold
      Koslow, Susan
      Kostotowski, Andrzeo
      Kraus, Erasmus
      Krause, Rudolf
      Kreismann, Illo
      Kress, R. N.
      Kroeber, A. L.
      Kuntz, Paul G.
      Kusch, Horst
      Kuylen, Krister van
    - Kaftal - Kahane, 1941-1963; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 29)
      Kaftal, George
      Kahane, Henry R.
      Kahane, Penuel P.
    - Kahr, Madlyn, 1962-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Kaiser - Kalinowski, 1955-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 31)
      Kaiser, Walter
      Kalinowski, Lech
    - Kantorwicz, E. H., 1951-1963, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Kapp - Kasack, 1941-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 33)
      Kapp, Ernest
      Kapp, Ida
      Karl, Adolph
      Karling, Sten
      Kasack, Hermann
    - Katzenellenbogen, Adolf, 1931-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 1-2)
    - Kauffmann, Hans, 1953-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Kaufmann, Emil, 1942-1953; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Kaufmann, Georg, 1960-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Kellam - Kelleher, 1952-1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 6)
      Kellam, Jack
      Kelleher, Patrick J.
    - Kennan - Kienitz, 1952-1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 7)
      Kennan, George F.
      Kessler, Clemencia Hand
      Kienitz, John F.
    - Kimball, Fiske, 1941-1955; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - King - Kisch, 1946-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 9)
      King, Edward L.
      King, L.G.T.
      Kisch, Guido
    - Kitzinger - Klauser, 1955-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 10)
      Kitzinger, Ernst
      Klauser, Theodor
    - Klein, Robert, 1957-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 11)